<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WebLogic Deploy Tooling</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/index.html</link>
    <description>WebLogic Deploy Tooling WebLogic Deploy Tooling (WDT) makes it easy to stand up WebLogic environments and perform domain lifecycle operations in a repeatable fashion based on a metadata model that can be treated as source and evolve as the project evolves.&#xA;Many organizations use WebLogic Server, with or without other Oracle Fusion Middleware components, to run their enterprise applications. And, as more and more of these organizations move toward Continuous Delivery of their applications, the importance of automated configuration application deployment grows. This automation is often implemented using the WebLogic Scripting Tool (WLST) configuration and deployment scripting language, but this is challenging. Such scripts must be carefully updated as the project evolves or the project is deployed to different environments, such as test to production.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Concepts</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/concepts/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/concepts/index.html</guid>
      <description>Concepts Archive FileThe section that discusses the structure and content of the WDT archive file.&#xA;Metadata ModelThe section that discusses the high-level concepts of the WDT model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User Guide</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/index.html</guid>
      <description>User Guide The User Guide provides detailed information about installing and using WebLogic Deploy Tools.&#xA;Install WDTThis section describes how to download and install WDT and what versions of Java and WebLogic Server it supports.&#xA;WDT ToolsThis section covers the tools that make up WDT.&#xA;Target environmentsThis section covers advanced features to target your WDT model to a specific environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samples</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/samples/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/samples/index.html</guid>
      <description>These typical use case scenarios show you how some common configurations can be represented in the model.&#xA;Customizing the Administration ServerConfigure the Administration Server using a domain model.&#xA;Modeling a configured clusterA domain model with a typical configuration for a configured cluster.&#xA;Modeling a WTC configurationA domain model with a typical configuration for a WebLogic Tuxedo Connector.&#xA;Modeling a JDBC data sourceA domain model with a typical configuration for a JDBC data source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Guide</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/index.html</guid>
      <description>Developer Guide The Developer Guide provides information for developers who want to understand or contribute to the code.&#xA;Project structureDescribes the WDT project structure.&#xA;Feature implementationHow specific features are implemented.&#xA;Alias definitionsHow the WDT aliases work.&#xA;Build WebLogic Deploy ToolingHow to build WDT from source.&#xA;Building CRD schemasHow to build the CRD schemas&#xA;WDT project release processHow releases are created from WDT source code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.3.9 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1837 - Added documentation for the tool exit codes to clarify an issue brought up in GitHub issue #1663. #1838 - Added a note to the Known Limitations page about delete ordering described in GitHub issue #1664. #1841 - Changed the alias definition for the WLDF ScriptAction folder’s Properties attribute so that it is written to the model file as a map instead of a string. #1845 - Added support for the RmiForwarding folders added in WebLogic Server 15.1.1. Bug Fixes #1835 - Fixed an issue that was causing Network Access Point deletion to fail (GitHub issue #1663). #1836 - Worked around the SSH issue for uploading files to an SSH server running Windows, removing the previously documented limitation. #1839 - Fixed the name of the CorsExposedHeader attribute (which was previously CorExposedHeader) in the RestfulManagementServices folder. #1840 - Fixed the alias file online MBean type for the LogFilter folder. #1842,#1843 - Fixed alias type issues with several attributes in the RestfulManagementServices folder. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>