<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>User Guide on WebLogic Deploy Tooling</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in User Guide on WebLogic Deploy Tooling</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:54 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Install WDT</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/install/</guid>
      <description>Download and install the software The WebLogic Deploy Tooling project repository is located at https://github.com/oracle/weblogic-deploy-tooling.
Binary distributions of the weblogic-deploy.zip installer can be downloaded from the GitHub Releases page.
 To install the software, simply unzip the weblogic-deploy.zip installer on a machine that has the desired versions of WebLogic Server installed. After being unzipped, the software is ready to use, just set the JAVA_HOME environment variable to point to a Java 7 or higher JDK and the shell scripts are ready to run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Target environments</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/target_env/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/target_env/</guid>
      <description>The Discover Domain and Prepare Model Tools allow you to customize the model and other files produced to be compatible with a specific target environment. Options for a target environment may include:
 Using model tokens for some attributes in the model. See Model tokens. Using Kubernetes secrets for credentials in the model. Applying filters to the model. See Model filters. Creating additional configuration files for the target system.  Specifying a target environment Each tool specifies a target environment using the command-line argument -target &amp;lt;target-name&amp;gt;, where &amp;lt;target-name&amp;gt; refers to a pre-configured target environment, or a user-defined environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
