<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Developer Guide on WebLogic Deploy Tooling</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Developer Guide on WebLogic Deploy Tooling</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:54 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project structure</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/project-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/project-structure/</guid>
      <description>This project is structured using the Standard Directory Layout for Maven projects, with two child modules, core, alias-test, system-test, and installer. In addition, there is a documentation directory containing project documentation.
The core module contains the main source code for the project. core includes Jython modules and Java classes, as well as typedef files, alias definitions, and the message bundle.
The system-test and alias-test modules contain test suites for verifying pull requests and nightly regression testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feature implementation</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/feature-impl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/feature-impl/</guid>
      <description>This document describes how specific features of WebLogic Deploy Tooling are implemented in the source code.
Creator and Deployer class hierarchies The creation of individual folders and attributes within the topology section of the domain model is accomplished using subclasses of the Jython class Creator, in the module wlsdeploy.tool.create.creator.py. The Creator class provides base methods to recurse through nested folders in the domain model, create or update those folders, and set or update their attributes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alias definitions</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/alias-definitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/alias-definitions/</guid>
      <description>WebLogic Deploy Tool uses a set of JSON configuration files to map folders and attributes in the model to the corresponding WLST MBeans and their attributes. These mappings are referred as &amp;lsquo;aliases&amp;rsquo; throughout the project code and documentation. Each element in the alias definition file has detailed properties that assist in this mapping.
The model&amp;rsquo;s folder and attribute names usually match the names of the corresponding elements in WLST. For cases where the names of WLST elements may change across WebLogic Server releases, the names should match the names in the 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build WebLogic Deploy Tool</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/buildwdt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/buildwdt/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites You will need the following software installed in your local build environment:
 Oracle WebLogic Server installation version 12.2.1 and later JDK version 8 Maven 3 and later  Specify the WLST location Execution of the unit tests requires a WebLogic Server installation, because the tests must be run within WLST.
The WLST directory can be specified in one of two ways:
  Specify the -Dunit-test-wlst-dir=&amp;lt;wlst-directory&amp;gt; on the mvn command line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building CRD schemas</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/crd-schemas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/crd-schemas/</guid>
      <description>The structure of the kubernetes and verrazzano sections of the WDT model are described by schemas based on the Custom Resource Definitions (CRDs) for those products. This is different from other sections of the model that use the alias framework to describe their structures.
NOTE: Verrazzano support is deprecated in WDT 4.0.0.
These schemas are used during model validation to check that folder and attribute names are valid. The Model Help Tool uses them to list the contents of folders and details about their attributes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WDT project release process</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/releaseprocess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/releaseprocess/</guid>
      <description>This document describes the process that should be followed to create a WebLogic Deploy Tooling (WDT) release.
Prerequisites  A local installation of WebLogic Server 12.2.1.x must be available. The person running the release process must have admin privileges on the WebLogic Deploy Tooling GitHub repo because the release process pushes to the master branch directly. The person running the release process needs to create a GitHub Personal Access Token for the repository with (at least) the repo:status, repo_deployment, public_repo, and security_events privileges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribute to WDT</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/developer/contribute/</guid>
      <description>Oracle welcomes contributions to this repository from anyone.
If you want to submit a pull request to fix a bug or enhance an existing feature, first open an issue and link to that issue when you submit your pull request.
If you have any questions about a possible submission, feel free to open an issue too.
Contributing to the WebLogic Deploy repository Pull requests can be made under The Oracle Contributor Agreement (OCA).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
