<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shared functionality on WebLogic Deploy Tooling</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/tools/shared/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shared functionality on WebLogic Deploy Tooling</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:36:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/tools/shared/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Online operations</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/tools/shared/online/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/tools/shared/online/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WebLogic Deploy Tooling supports online operations against running WebLogic Server-based domains.  By definition, this&#xA;means that WDT is acting as a remote client to the domain&amp;rsquo;s admin server&amp;ndash;even if the WDT tool is running on the same&#xA;machine as the admin server.  The main point being that WDT and the server may or may not be using the same Oracle Home.&#xA;This becomes an even more likely scenario when using the &lt;code&gt;-remote&lt;/code&gt; option or when using SSH-based remote access.  This&#xA;document describes the general behavior you should expect when running WDT tools in online mode.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSH support</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/tools/shared/ssh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/tools/shared/ssh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WDT 4.0 introduces the ability to perform online operations remotely using SSH to provide access to the remote&#xA;server&amp;rsquo;s file system.  SSH support is provided by the SSHJ Java library and is integrated in a way intended to support&#xA;a both user/password-based and private/public key-based authentication, a wide variety of key encryption formats, and&#xA;a reasonable set of defaults to minimize the number of inputs required for typical usage scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tool Exit Codes</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/tools/shared/exit_codes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/tools/shared/exit_codes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WebLogic Deploy Tooling uses operating system exit codes to determine whether the command succeeded or not.  WDT&#xA;follows the normal conventions exiting with a zero exit code when the tool completes successfully.  When various&#xA;situations are encountered, non-zero exit codes are used to communicate what happened to the user. The exit codes&#xA;and their meanings are as shown in the table below.  Unless otherwise noted, all tools use these exit codes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
