<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Release Notes on WebLogic Deploy Tooling</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Release Notes on WebLogic Deploy Tooling</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes 3.2.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.1/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.2.1  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #1465 - Initial, limited i18n translation bundles added.  Bug Fixes  #1466 - Updated Server and ServerTemplate aliases to add new 14.1.2 offline attributes. #1467 - Updated CoherenceSystemResource aliases to add new 14.1.2 SecuredProduction online attribute. #1468 - Fixed an error related to tool initialization with WebLogic Server versions earlier than 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes 3.2.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.2.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #1450 - Added alias updates for April 2023 PSUs for 12.2.1.3, 12.2.1.4, and 14.1.1. #1454 - Added aliases for new fields introduced 14.1.2. #1457 - Deprecated system-elements section of typedef files and replaced it with a new discover-filters section that supports filtering named elements in most top-level folders. #1458 - Updated Model and Archive documentation to reflect the current state of the code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes 3.1.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.1.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes  #1431 - Added new OPSSInitialization section to domainInfo in order to support ODI and OIG domain creation. #1432 - Added database connectivity check to validate RCU database connection details prior to creating a domain using RCU schemas when not running RCU. #1434 - Added JSON output of restart and non-dynamic change information (#1154) #1438 - Deprecated the use of all RCU-related arguments that provide database connectivity information with the Create Domain tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.0.4</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.4/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.0.4  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #1422: Fixed a bug in online discovery of the Cluster attribute of ServerTemplate. #1425: Fixed a bug for online remote discovery causing SSL cipher suites to show up in 14.1.1 even when it was set to the default value.  Known Issues </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes 3.0.3</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.3/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.0.3  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #1412: Fixed a bug in the Prepare Model integration with WKTUI. #1413: Fixed a number of internationalization message-related issues. #1414: Fixed a bug with wallet collection during discovery of a Proxy data source. #1416: Fixed a bug in the handling of mail session properties with credentials that was causing a Jython AttributeError (Issue #1415).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes 3.0.2</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.2/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.0.2  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #1405: Corrected some issues with the Windows shell scripts where they were not properly handling paths with spaces. #1409: Corrected a bug where a wallet deprecation message was still being logged as a warning. #1411: Corrected a bug where wallet extraction handling with multiple archive files was happening in the wrong order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.0.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.1/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.0.1  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #1396: Added additional validation to the RCUDbInfo section. #1398: Corrected a bug introduced in 3.0.0 that broke validation of sparse models with dynamic clusters.  Known Issues  When running discoverDomain with the -remote flag, there are several MBeans that are not being properly handled that will result in INFO level messages that look similar to the example shown below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.0.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.0.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features  #1355: Added -remote option to the deployApps tool that supports deploying applications and shared libraries from a remote machine. (Issue #1312) #1355: Added -remote option to the updateDomain tool that allows configuration changes not requiring archive file changes (except for applications and shared libraries) to be made from a remote machine. (Issue #1167) #1365: Added new verrazzano section of the model that can be used to augment/override the YAML files generated by the Verrazzano-related -target options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2.4.4</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.4/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 2.4.4  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #1361: Resolved issue where the custom Coherence configuration file was not placed in the WebLogic Server domain&amp;rsquo;s expected location.  Known Issues  Due to the changes made for WDT-663 in WDT 2.4.0, the resulting remotely discovered model contains extra fields that would not normally be there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2.4.3</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.3/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 2.4.3  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #1356: Resolved Issue where the new ATP Database URL format was causing connections to fail.  Known Issues  Due to the changes made for WDT-663 in WDT 2.4.0, the resulting remotely discovered model contains extra fields that would not normally be there. This is an area of ongoing work to clean up the online aliases to not depend on these extra remote calls to produce a clean model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2.4.2</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.2/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 2.4.2  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features None
Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #1241: Resolved Issue #1240 that was causing a NullPointerException with discoverDomain. #1252: Reworked the unicode handling to resolve customer issues with 14.1.1 when using non-ASCII characters.  Known Issues  Due to the changes made for WDT-663 in WDT 2.4.0, the resulting remotely discovered model contains extra fields that would not normally be there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2.4.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.1/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 2.4.1  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features  None  Other Changes None
Bug Fixes  #1237: Resolved an issue where the tools supporting the -target parameter were doing target-related work even if the parameter was not specified.  Known Issues  Due to the changes made for WDT-663 in WDT 2.4.0, the resulting remotely discovered model contains extra fields that would not normally be there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2.4.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.0/</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 2.4.0  Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues  Major New Features  None  Other Changes  #1193 - Added support for changing the RCU Data Source type during JRF domain creation (WDT-636). #1210 - Improved the speed of remote discovery by bypassing remote calls to determine if a field was set (WDT-663). #1218 - Added -target support for WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 4.0 to generate the domain and cluster schema resources.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
