<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Release Notes :: WebLogic Deploy Tooling</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/index.html</link>
    <description>Changes in Release 4.4.0 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1854 - Added the merge.server-start-arguments to the tool.properties file with a default of true. Setting the value to false will disable the merging and simply replace any existing value to the model value. Bug Fixes #1847 - Fixed a number of attributes to correct the alias setting for uses_path_tokens to give more accurate information for the upcoming WKT UI model editor. #1848, #1855 - Fixed a number of attributes that are delimited strings in WLST to allow the use of lists in the model. #1849 - Fixed the handling of the JMS ForeignServer ConnectionURL in the Create Domain and Update Domain Tools. #1850 - Fixed a number of attributes that are delimited strings with name-value pairs in WLST to allow the use of YAML dictionaries in the model. #1851 - Added the merging handler use in ServerStart Arguments processing to SystemComponentStart Arguments. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.3.9</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.9/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.9/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.3.9 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1837 - Added documentation for the tool exit codes to clarify an issue brought up in GitHub issue #1663. #1838 - Added a note to the Known Limitations page about delete ordering described in GitHub issue #1664. #1841 - Changed the alias definition for the WLDF ScriptAction folder’s Properties attribute so that it is written to the model file as a map instead of a string. #1845 - Added support for the RmiForwarding folders added in WebLogic Server 15.1.1. Bug Fixes #1835 - Fixed an issue that was causing Network Access Point deletion to fail (GitHub issue #1663). #1836 - Worked around the SSH issue for uploading files to an SSH server running Windows, removing the previously documented limitation. #1839 - Fixed the name of the CorsExposedHeader attribute (which was previously CorExposedHeader) in the RestfulManagementServices folder. #1840 - Fixed the alias file online MBean type for the LogFilter folder. #1842,#1843 - Fixed alias type issues with several attributes in the RestfulManagementServices folder. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.3.8</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.8/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.8/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.3.8 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes None&#xA;Bug Fixes #1833 - Fixed an issue with CLASSPATH handling where empty elements were present that caused Discover Domain to fail. #1834 - Fixed an issue with security provider handling that was causing Create Domain to fail. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.3.7</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.7/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.7/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.3.7 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1816 - Added support for 12.2.1.4, 14.1.1, and 14.1.2 July 2025 PSUs. #1826 - Improved support for DBClientData directories by adding model support. #1827 - Removed Verrazzano support that was deprecated in 4.0.0. Various - Added support for 15.1.1 GA release. Bug Fixes #1811 - Fixed an issue to allow support for null default values for attributes during discovery #1830 - Fixed 12.2.1.3 alias values for OracleIdentityCloudIntegrator #1831 - Fixed variable injection for security providers Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.3.6</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.6/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.6/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.3.6 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes None&#xA;Bug Fixes #1806 - Reverted SnakeYAML to version 2.3 to restore JDK 7 support. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.3.5</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.5/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.5/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.3.5 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1802 - Added support for the 12.2.1.4, 14.1.1, and 14.1.2 April 2025 PSUs. Bug Fixes #1803 - Fixed the Update Domain Tool documentation to list -output_dir in the list of supported arguments. #1804 - Addressed CVE-2020-36843 by upgrading sshj to a version that removes the dependency on eddsa and removing eddsa from the WDT installer. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.3.4</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.4/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.4/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.3.4 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1792 - Segregated ServerTemplate keystores in the archive file. #1798 - Added ClusterAddress, ListenAddress, InterfaceAddress, and MulticastAddress to the WKO filter when using Discover Domain and Prepare Model tools with the -target argument. #1799 - Added the oracle_database_admin_role field to the RCUDbInfo section for users that need to use a role that is not SYSDBA. Bug Fixes #1784 - Prevent Discover Domain tool from trying to discover passwords unless the user specified to do so. #1785 - Change logging level from INFO to FINE for unrecognized attributes when using online operations. #1786 - Fixed RCU discovery issue to properly handle passwords. #1787 - Fixed issue with WKO filter to eliminate errors when traversing the model. #1788 - Restored internal method call to compare WLS versions in the Discover Domain tool. #1789 - Fixing issues with the -target wko filter. #1790 - Add missing 14.1.2 JDK version information to the installation documentation. #1794 - Fixing an issue with the RCU password not being properly decrypted while trying to validate the RCU data when running the Create Domain tool. #1795 - Fixing a bug introduced by change #1792 that was causing an error when discovering Server and ServerTemplate keystores. #1796 - Fixed an issue where the datasource password was not being decrypted properly when using the Discover Domain tool with the -discover_passwords argument. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.3.3</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.3/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.3/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.3.3 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1780 - Added new -discover_rcu_datasources option to the Discover Domain Tool to help with migration use cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.3.2</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.2/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.2/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.3.2 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1778 - Added preliminary support for using an enhanced offline isSet() method when determining whether to write computed fields to the model during offline discovery. Once the enhancement is available in a 14.1.2 PSU, we will complete the support. Bug Fixes #1773 - Reduced the logging level of a message about removing attributes from the model to reduce the amount of noise on stdout. #1775 - Fixed Discover Domain Tool handling of server keystore files when running with -skip_archive. #1776 - Fixed issues with the ManagedExecutorServiceTemplate, ManagedScheduledExecutorServiceTemplate, and ManagedThreadFactoryTemplate folders so that they can be used in models. #1777 - Fixed Create Domain Tool so write the domain’s mode-related attributes upfront before the initial call to writeDomain() so that the dynamically computed fields are properly persisted in config.xml. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.3.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.1/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.3.1 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1771 - Added support for January 2025 PSUs for 12.2.1.4, 14.1.1, and 14.1.2. Bug Fixes #1762, #1764 - Fixed issues with causing Discover Domain to generate attribute not supported log entries for deprecated attributes. #1763 - Documented WebLogic Server Bug 37443991 as a known limitation. #1765 - Fixed AttributeError when running Discover Domain with either -skip_archive or -remote (GitHub Issue 1607). #1766 - Fixed AttributeError when running Discover Domain with either -skip_archive or -remote on different archive types (GitHub Issue 1608). #1767 - Fixed Discover Domain command-line argument validation that allows both -skip_archive and -remote to be specified when they are mutually exclusive. #1768 - Improved default value detection for Discover Domain when running against WebLogic Server 14.1.2. #1769 - Cleaned up offline Discover Domain to exclude the JavaHome attribute in the NMProperties folder. #1770 - Fixed secure mode detection to work properly in WebLogic Server 14.1.2. This is critical to reducing the number of attributes that show up in the model when using Discover Domain in offline mode. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.3.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.0/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.3.0/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.3.0 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1731, #1735, #1736, #1738, #1743, #1748 - Updated aliases for WebLogic Server 14.1.2 GA release. #1732 - Changed default value when using -target to include the domain’s bin directory contents. #1737 - Optimized offline discovery of default values in 14.1.2. #1739 - Added aliases for SNMPAgent, SNMPDeploymentAgent, EJBContainer, and Cluster’s JtaRemoteDomain folders. #1741 - Added support for deploying and discovering customer resources. #1746 - Added support for the WebLogic Server 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1 October 2024 PSUs. #1750 - Changed file path resolution to not convert symbolic links to the actual paths. #1751 - Changed JDK validation to allow the user to run WDT tools with OpenJDK and removed broken support for GraalVM. #1752 - Moved away from using jline’s deprecated jansi provider to using the jni provider. #1758 - Enhanced Create Domain Tool to allow creating a JRF domain using fully specified RCU Data Sources in the resources:/JDBCSystemResource section of the model without requiring the domainInfo:/RCUDbInfo section. #1760 - Modified WDT’s usage of JAXB classes to prepare for supporting the Jakarta EE 9+ of JAXB runtime. Bug Fixes #1732 - Fixed bad error message when WLST assign() invocation fails. #1734 - Fixed validation error caused by trying to validate prior to resolving tokens. #1744 - Squelched SLF4J startup messages from printing to stderr. #1748 - Fixed target injector paths causing discovery to fail with sub-deployments. #1749 - Fixed JMS Foreign Server discovery issue when the URL is not using a file, http, or https protocol. #1753 - Cleaned up exiting from the interactive Model Help Tool using Control-D. #1755 - Fixed bug with command-line handling of the WDT encryption passphrase from stdin. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.2.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.2.1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.2.1/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.2.1 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1717, #1728 - Extended the API integration between WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI and WDT to pass back the encrypted passwords when running the Prepare Model Tool from the WebLogic Kubernetes Toolkit UI. #1722 - Added logic to detect a situation where the user specified in domainInfo:/AdminUserName is also listed in the topology:/Security/User list of users and update the topology:/Security/User user’s Password field to be the same as that specified in domainInfo:/AdminPassword. #1723 - Added support for the WebLogic Server 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1 July 2024 PSUs. Bug Fixes #1713 - Added logic at startup to detect when WDT logging is not properly configured. #1715 - Fixed a bug where the domainInfo:/OPSSWalletPassphrase field was not properly handled when using the Prepare Model Tool or when using the Discover Domain Tool with the -target argument. #1716 - Fixed the Discover Domain Tool documentation to add missing command-line arguments. #1718 - Fixed an issue with the NativeVersionEnabled attribute of NMProperties not working correctly when running the Update Domain Tool. #1720 - Fixed an issue with RCU pre-check error handling that was causing an unhandled Jython error. #1721 - Fixed a bug in the SSH directory listing command for a remote Unix machine. #1724 - Fixed an off-by-one error when using the Archive Helper Tool’s remove custom command with a name that starts with wlsdeploy/custom/ or config/wlsdeploy/custom/ that was causing the specified location to not be removed. #1727, #1729 - Fixed an issue with Create Domain Tool’s RCU pre-check functionality that was causing a Jython AttributeException for set when the STB DataSource was defined in the resources:/JDBCSystemResource section of the model and specifying one or more JDBC driver properties. #1730 - Fixed an issue where an application or library deployment plan was not being collected when the SourcePath contained an excluded location like @@ORACLE_HOME@@. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.2.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.2.0/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.2.0/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.2.0 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1682 - Added support for discovering built-in security provider data in online mode. This includes DefaultAuthenticator users and groups, XACMLAuthorizer policies, XACMLRoleMapper roles, and DefaultCredentialMapper user/password credential mappings. As with other discovery features, default values are filtered out and will not appear in the model. By default, discovering users and credential mappings require the use of WDT encryption so that no clear text passwords are stored in the model or variable files. #1682 - Normalized XACMLRoleMapper role handling by removing the previous discovery of XACMLRoleMapper roles (that was not working with newer versions of WebLogic anyway) and removing version limitations during provisioning. #1682 - Deprecated the -use_encryption command-line argument and replaced it with -passphrase_prompt to make the purpose of the argument clearer. #1682 - Relaxed the JDK 8 requirement to use WDT encryption. Later versions of JDK 7 have the necessary algorithm support so now WDT determines at startup whether the underlying JDK supports WDT encryption or not. #1682 - Used the values of the -admin_user and provided password to populate the domainInfo:/AdminUserName and domainInfo:/AdminPassword fields when discovering security provider data. #1688 - Enhanced variable tokenization support to include passwords in discovered security provider data. #1689 - Added the ability to discover the OPSS wallet when running in online mode. #1693 - Changed the wko, wko-dii (deprecated), and wko-pv target values to refer to the latest versions instead of WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 3 versions. Added wko3, wko3-dii, and wko3-pv to accommodate users that still require the ability to use these older versions. #1697 - Added support for the Prepare Model Tool to preserve any one-way hashed passwords in the model. #1700 - Added support for storing XACML policy and role definitions that could not be converted to their original policy and role expressions as XACML files in the archive file. Bug Fixes #1687 - Fixed a problem with the Discover Domain Tool not properly handling Data Source user names with spaces with older versions of WebLogic Server. #1690 - Fixed a problem with determining the default security realm name that caused it to always be myrealm. #1692 - Fixed a misleading error message when the model points to an application outside of the archive file that does not exist. #1695 - Fixed an issue where the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator domain.yaml was including a placeholder for the domainHome attribute in all cases so that the WebLogic Image Tool could populate it when creating the image. This was occurring even in use cases where the WebLogic Image Tool did not have this information. WDT no longer does this and will only include the domainHome in the case where the user has specified it on the command line, or in the kubernetes section of the model. #1698 - Fixed issues with the new messages related to the security provider data discovery features. #1701 - Moved the TestSummaryHandler logging class out of the installer since it is only meant for supporting unit tests. #1702 - Fixed a bug in deployment plan discovery for exploded applications. #1703 - Fixed a bug in discovery of domainBin scripts. #1705 - Added missing validation for the WLSUserPasswordCredentialMappings section. #1706 - Fixed a validation bug that was causing lax validation to fail when archive entries were missing. #1707 - Fixed a bug in the handling of the ActiveContextHandlerEntry attribute of an Auditor security provider. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.1.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.1.1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.1.1/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.1.1 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1685 - Filtered out the default OptionalFeatures folders when they have no attributes so that they do not show up in the online discovered model. Bug Fixes #1677 - Fixed a bug where creating a user with extra attributes would result in invalid LDIFT entries. #1678 - Fixed a bug that was causing errors when deploying a new application and the server required a restart. #1679 - Fixed a bug where the SSHJ libraries (that only work with JDK 8 and later) were causing the tools to fail when running with JDK 7. #1680 - Fixed the DataSourceLogFile and WebServerLog folders default value for the DateFormatPattern attribute for WLS versions prior to 12.2.1 so that they no longer show up in the online discovered model. #1681 - Worked around a pre-12.2.1 WLST bug that was preventing the online tools from determining the server’s WLS version. #1683 - Fixed a bug with the Model Help Tool where our use of JLine libraries (that only work with JDK 8 and later) were causing the Model Help tool to fail when run with JDK 7. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.1.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.1.0/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.1.0/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.1.0 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1668 - Added new discover passwords feature that allows the user to discover passwords and store them in the model in encrypted format. Bug Fixes #1675 - Fixed a bug with replacing environment variable tokens on Windows. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.0.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.0.1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.0.1/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.0.1 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1664 - Added support for the OptionalFeatureDeployment top-level folder. #1665, #1667 - Formalized support for both the replicated config/wlsdeploy/custom/ and non-replicated wlsdeploy/custom locations. Added support in the Archive Helper Tool and tweaked the validation message to only notify the user if they are only using the non-replicated location. #1669 - Enhanced the WLS Policy support to allow users to modify built-in policies. #1674 - Added 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1 April 2024 PSU support. Bug Fixes #1666 - Fixed a bug with extracting the WebLogic Remote Console extension that caused an error if the archive file includes a directory entry. #1670 - Worked around a Jython 2.2.1 bug with posixpath.isfile() where it was returning False when the answer should have been True. #1672 - Added None checks around plan file name calculations. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 4.0.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.0.0/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-4.0.0/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 4.0.0 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features #1481 - Added new Verify SSH Tool to support testing an environment for using the new SSH support. #1516 - Added SSH support for Discover Domain, Update Domain, and Deploy Apps Tools that will allow these tools to work against a WebLogic domain running on a remote machine. #1548, #1553, #1556 - Revamped the Model Help Tool to improve the semantics and behavior of interactive mode. Added online mode support. Fixed CRDs to work consistently with alias folders and attributes. #1550 - Refactored the archive file and moved content extraction into $DOMAIN_HOME/config/wlsdeploy for some types to take advantage of existing Pack/Unpack behavior and admin server to managed server replications capabilities. #1584 - Added support for creating WebLogic authorization policies during domain creation (GitHub issue #1496). #1641, #1643, #1644, #1645, #1646, #1647, #1648, #1650 - Overhauled Application and Library provisioning. As part of this overhaul, we have tried to define the semantics for non-archived application deployments, particularly with online Update Domain and Deploy Applications tools. For non-archive applications/libraries, online deployment of binaries outside of the archive will always assume that the binaries are available to the Administration Server at the model-specified paths. Neither the -remote or SSH options will attempt to upload the non-archived binaries. #1654, #1655, #1656, #1658, #1659, #1661 - Overhaul of the Create Domain Tool’s support for running RCU and applying RCU-related changes to the RCU Data Sources. Other Changes #1544 - Consolidated multiple internal WLST helper methods to get an MBean. #1552 - Added typedef support for discoverExcludedBinariesList to allow OIG to add a custom application in the Oracle Home to the archive file. #1564 - Added Discover Domain Tool support for discovering the WebLogic Remote Console domain extension. #1568 - Added the ability to remove MBean assignments in the model by setting them to null or empty (GitHub issue #1483). #1569 - Improved version handling for online operations to always use the server’s WebLogic Server version. #1572 - Enhanced the wlsdeploy.debugToStdout system property to also include exception stacktraces when set to true. This will help WebLogic Kubernetes Operator users running into WDT issues to see the details normally hidden in the log files. #1583 - Eliminated the -domain_home argument from tools running in online mode. #1586 - Simplified variable injector configuration and customization. #1587 - Removed deprecated RCU-related command-line arguments from the Create Domain Tool. #1588 - Deprecated the domainInfo section’s OPSSSecrets attribute and replaced it with OPSSWalletPassphrase to better represent the purpose of the attribute. #1592 - Deprecated Verrazzano support. #1598 - Added support for online wallet distribution to managed servers in upcoming versions of WebLogic Server. #1599 - Added support for the 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1 January 2024 PSUs. #1605 - Deprecated the Deploy Applications Tool. The intention going forward is that users should be able to use the Update Domain Tool, which already does everything that the Deploy Applications Tool does and more. #1613 - Added ability to use variable tokens in the SAML 2 data initialization property files that will be replaced during domain creation or update processing. #1614 - Updated Discover Domain Tool to overwrite existing variable and archive files if they already exist. #1616 - Improved RCUDbInfo validation in Create Domain tool. #1630 - Replaced the -variable_property_file argument in the Inject Variables tool with -variable_file #1653 - Added support for creating a domain with password digests enabled and users that are properly provisioned so that you do not need to delete and recreate the users after the server is started. #1654 - Added OAM and OIG domain typedefs to support the Oracle Identity Management team’s Kubernetes offering. Please be aware that these are not intended to be general-purpose, WDT typedefs and are only supported by the Oracle Identity Management team in the context of their Kubernetes offering! #1654 - Deprecated the RCUDbInfo section’s databaseType attribute and replaced it with oracle_database_connection_type. Bug Fixes #1555 - Fixed issues with creating and discovering UnixMachine objects in online mode. #1562 - Added missing default values for RCUDbInfo attributes. #1563 - Fixed an issue with Compare Model where it was trying to compare an invalid field. #1565 - Suppressed logging of domain typedef information by the exit context used to handle unexpected errors. #1575 - Added support for storing the CreateTableDDLFile script referenced by the TransactionLogJDBCStore in the archive file. #1579 - Fixed an issue that limited the number of secret keys that could be referenced by the model. #1584 - Fixed an issue where online updates that required restarts were using a 12.2.1+ API even with older versions. #1603 - Fixed a bug related to online WLST error message formatting. #1608 - Fixed a bug in creating Security groups that are members of another group. #1610 - Fixed a bug where the Create Domain and Update Domain Tools were trying to create a security provider that is not valid in the current WebLogic Server version. #1615 - Fixed an issue where certain errors during online update or deploy operations could leave a pending edit state that caused subsequent invocations to fail due to the pending edit state. #1619 - Fixed a bug that was causing offline discovery to omit the LogRotation attribute when the value was set to none. #1631 - Fixed an issue where the Update Domain and the Deploy Applications Tools running in online mode were trying to call start on an application when earlier changes required a server restart. #1634 - Fixed an issue with the ResourceManagement MBean when running the Discover Domain Tool in online mode with WebLogic Server 14.1.1 and newer. #1636 - Fixed an issue with Update Domain and Deploy Applications Tools when using the -remote option that was causing a TODO message to be generated when there was nothing for the user to do. #1638 - Fixed an issue with the Update Domain and Deploy Applications Tools where the application specified a PlanDir and a PlanPath but the online deployment was ignoring the PlanDir, resulting in a file does not exist error when attempting to deploy the application. #1642 - Fixed deployment issues with deploying applications not included in an archive file. #1643 - Fixed an issue with Discover Domain where application/library path tokenization was preventing adding deployments to the archive file. #1657 - Fixed an issue with the JRF pre-check functionality of the Create Domain Tool where it was ignoring any Data Source overrides for the STB data source set in the model. #1659 - Fixed an issue with the Create Domain Tool where it was ignoring any Data Source overrides for the OPSS data source set in the model when fixing the jps-copfig.xml and jps-config-jse.xml files. #1660 - Fixed an issue with the Update Domain Tool running in online mode against a JRF domain that was causing extra analysis of applications and libraries that the JRF domain typedef declares as filtered. Known Issues SSH support requires a reasonably recent version of Bouncy Castle. WDT picks up Bouncy Castle from WLST so, for example, the 12.2.1.4.0 GA release fails with the following error, as mentioned at https://github.com/hierynomus/sshj/issues/895 . Applying a recent PSU should resolve the issue for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.5.4</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.5.4/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.5.4/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.5.4 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1600 - Added alias updates to support the Jan 2024 PSUs. Bug Fixes #1607 - Fixed an issue with assigning groups to parent groups. #1620 - Fixed an issue that caused an attribute with the WLST value none to be interpreted as a Python None. #1635 - Fixed an issue with the ResourceManagement attribute in WebLogic Server 14.1.1 and higher. Known Issues None</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.5.3</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.5.3/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.5.3/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.5.3 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1573 - Enhanced the wlsdeploy.debugToStdout system property to also include exception stacktraces when set to true. This will help WebLogic Kubernetes Operator users running into WDT issues to see the details normally hidden in the log files. Bug Fixes #1561 - Fixed a NullPointerException when there is missing fields in the RCUDbInfo section. #1590 - Fixed an issue with the ServiceProviderSingleLogoutRedirectUri attribute in the October 2023 PSUs for 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1 that was causing an error. #1590 - Fixed an issue with exception creation in 14.1.1 that was causing error messages not to be properly populated due to Jython 2.7.1 vararg method binding being broken. Known Issues None</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.5.2</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.5.2/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.5.2/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.5.2 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1557 - Added support for provisioning the WebLogic Remote Console domain extension WAR file. Bug Fixes #1547 - Fixed a bug with password validation causing a NullPointerException when the domainInfo section was missing from the model. #1554 - Fixed a problem where the Discover Domain tool would hang when running in online mode and an edit lock exists. Known Issues None</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.5.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.5.1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.5.1/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.5.1 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes None&#xA;Bug Fixes #1542 - Fixed a Prepare Model issue related to the new password validation feature introduced in 3.5.0. Known Issues None</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.5.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.5.0/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.5.0/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.5.0 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1535 - Changed the timing for extracting the archive file’s custom folder to support storing custom WebLogic Server security provider JAR files (GitHub issue #1512). #1537, #1539 - Cleaned up user password validation and extended it to support customizing the default settings using the model’s SystemPasswordValidator settings, if present. See https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/tools/create/#user-password-validation for details (GitHub issue #1510). Bug Fixes #1538 - Fixed online discovery of Coherence Cache Config files if the fix for Bug 35969096 is present. Known Issues Prepare Model fails if the model contains tokenized passwords. See https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/userguide/limitations/limitations/ for the current set of known limitations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.4.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.4.0/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.4.0/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.4.0 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1521 - Added alias changes to accommodate October 2023 PSUs for WebLogic Server versions 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1. #1525 - Added missing MBeans to better support the WebLogic Remote Console. #1527 - Added missing Security Provider attributes to better support the WebLogic Remote Console. #1530 - Refactored the handling of Coherence Custom Cluster and Cache Config files to correct the behavior and expand online update and discover capabilities. One side effect is that the Discover Domain tool when run in online mode will generate warnings and skip discovery of Coherence Cache Config folders. This is due to a shortcoming in WebLogic Server’s Coherence configuration support that is tracked by Bug 35969096. Bug Fixes #1522 - Fixed issues related to unicode handling that were causing errors processing typedef files. #1526 - Fixed an issue that was preventing custom typedefs from working properly (WDT-771/GitHub Issue #1506). #1528 - Fixed an issue that was causing the standalone Validate Model tool to write credentials to the log with certain models. Fixed an issue that was causing log level escalation (WDT-783). #1529 - Fixed an issue for boolean attributes with null default values. This issue was causing Discover Domain to incorrectly treat attributes whose values were False to be omitted from the discovered model. Known Issues None</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.3.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.3.0/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.3.0/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.3.0 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1517 - Added a postCreateRcuSchemasScript element to the typedef file definitions to accommodate extra schema patching work required for Oracle Identity Governance domain creation. #1519 - Added rcu_admin_user field to the domainInfo:/RCUDbInfo section to replace rcu_db_user, which is now deprecated and will be removed in a future release. This field is optional and will default to the appropriate admin user name: admin when using an ATP database and SYS otherwise. Bug Fixes #1518 - Fixed an issue when using an ATP database as the RCU schema repository that was causing config/fmwconfig/jps-config.xml to contain a clear text password after JRF domain creation. Known Issues None</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.2.6</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.6/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.6/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.2.6 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1514 - Added the ability to disable the RCU drop schema step when running Create Domain with -run_rcu. Bug Fixes #1511 - Fixed an error message to make it more helpful. #1513 - Fixed issues with sparse RCU Data Source template merging when creating JRF domains. Known Issues None</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.2.5</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.5/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.5/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.2.5 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes None&#xA;Bug Fixes #1506 - Fixed an issue with online discovery of the JMS ErrorDestination attribute (GitHub #1494). #1507 - Added documentation for the WDT Discover Domain tool’s limitation regarding users and groups in the DefaultAuthenticator (GitHub #1493). #1508 - Fixed an issue with Update Domain that was causing the Oracle JDBC driver to throw FileNotFoundException when using a JRF domain with an ATP database. #1509 - Fixed an issue with online discovery of custom security providers that caused the implementation class name to be added to the model instead of the interface class name (GitHub #1495).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.2.4</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.4/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.4/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.2.4 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1503 - Added the EnableJMSStoreDBPersistence and EnableJTATLogDBPersistence attributes to domainInfo, which allow JRF domains to automatically convert template-defined JMS and JTA stores from File stores to Database stores during domain creation. This feature was added in support of Oracle Identity Governance domain creation. Bug Fixes None</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.2.3</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.3/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.3/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.2.3 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1496 - Added a post-createDomain script element to the typedef file definitions to accommodate extra offline work required for Oracle Identity Governance domain creation. #1499 - Added updated translation bundle files. Bug Fixes #1486 - Fixed JSON parser issue in handling escaped newlines. #1488 - Worked around a Jython 2.2.1 issue where environment variables with a newline in their value caused remaining environment variable values to not be visible from Jython. #1490 - Fixed an issue with deprecation logging statements to ensure that the class and method names were logged properly. #1494 - Changed the language for some logging/error messages to make them clearer. #1495 - Reworded several log messages that were confusing to users and difficult to translate. #1497 - Fixed sh-based shell scripts to work properly on Solaris 10.x Bourne shell #1498 - Corrected the error message for a deploy-related error. Known Issues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.2.2</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.2/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.2/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.2.2 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1475 - Added support for upcoming SAML2 data initialization files in the archive file. #1476 - Added support for upcoming SAML2 data initialization files in the Discover Domain, Create Domain, and Update Domain tools. Bug Fixes #1482 - Fixed an issue related to secret naming that was causing the generated secret names to overlap in locations with multiple credential or password fields. #1483 - Filtered out the OPSSSecrets field in the domainInfo section of the model when targeting WebLogic Kubernetes Operator or Verrazzano MII and PV targets. #1484 - Fixed aliases for the 12.2.1.4 and 14.1.1 July 2023 PSU versions. Known Issues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.2.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.1/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.2.1 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1465 - Initial, limited i18n translation bundles added. Bug Fixes #1466 - Updated Server and ServerTemplate aliases to add new offline attributes in upcoming versions of WebLogic Server. #1467 - Updated CoherenceSystemResource aliases to add SecuredProduction online attribute used in upcoming versions of WebLogic Server. #1468 - Fixed an error related to tool initialization with WebLogic Server versions earlier than 12.2.1 (Issue #1466). #1469 - Corrected method names used for logging so that they are the same as the actual method name in which they are being used. #1470 - Fixed system-test test 35 to allow it to succeed when run on machines other than the Jenkins agents. #1471 - Fixed a discoverDomain issue that was causing errors while looking for SecureMode on WebLogic Server versions earlier than 12.2.1.1 (Issue #1467). Known Issues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.2.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.0/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.2.0/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.2.0 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1450 - Added alias updates for April 2023 PSUs for 12.2.1.3, 12.2.1.4, and 14.1.1. #1454 - Added aliases for new fields introduced in upcoming versions of WebLogic Server. #1457 - Deprecated system-elements section of typedef files and replaced it with a new discover-filters section that supports filtering named elements in most top-level folders. #1458 - Updated Model and Archive documentation to reflect the current state of the code. Bug Fixes #1459 - Fixed a type conversion issues for properties entries where boolean and integers were not being properly converted to strings in 14.1.1 and newer. Known Issues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.1.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.1.0/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.1.0/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.1.0 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes #1431 - Added new OPSSInitialization section to domainInfo in order to support ODI and OIG domain creation. #1432 - Added database connectivity check to validate RCU database connection details prior to creating a domain using RCU schemas when not running RCU. #1434 - Added JSON output of restart and non-dynamic change information (#1154) #1438 - Deprecated the use of all RCU-related arguments that provide database connectivity information with the Create Domain tool. Bug Fixes #1428 - Added command-line usage for OPSS Wallet related arguments to Create Domain. Enhanced the documentation to describe how to use the OPSS Wallet to recreate a domain that connects to existing RCU schemas. #1429 - Updated Discover Domain -target argument usage. Updated the documentation related to -target to reflect recent changes. #1436 - Fixed an issue with deleting machines created by a template. #1437 - Fixed offline discovery issues when discovering domains that have used slashes in their object names (e.g., SOA Suite) #1438 - Fixed issues where Create Domain RCU-related command-line arguments were not override model-supplied values. #1439 - Worked around a discovery issue for domains with the Trust Service Identity Asserter when the Oracle Home has not been patched to contain the security provider’s schema JAR file. Known Issues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.0.4</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.4/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.4/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.0.4 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes None&#xA;Bug Fixes #1422: Fixed a bug in online discovery of the Cluster attribute of ServerTemplate. #1425: Fixed a bug for online remote discovery causing SSL cipher suites to show up in 14.1.1 even when it was set to the default value. Known Issues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.0.3</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.3/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.3/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.0.3 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes None&#xA;Bug Fixes #1412: Fixed a bug in the Prepare Model integration with WKTUI. #1413: Fixed a number of internationalization message-related issues. #1414: Fixed a bug with wallet collection during discovery of a Proxy data source. #1416: Fixed a bug in the handling of mail session properties with credentials that was causing a Jython AttributeError (Issue #1415). #1419: Fixed open issue from previous releases regarding wlst attribute not defined errors in online remote discovery. #1420: Fixed a bug where a trailing slash on an application SourcePath would cause a empty ZIP file error. Known Issues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.0.2</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.2/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.2/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.0.2 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes None&#xA;Bug Fixes #1405: Corrected some issues with the Windows shell scripts where they were not properly handling paths with spaces. #1409: Corrected a bug where a wallet deprecation message was still being logged as a warning. #1411: Corrected a bug where wallet extraction handling with multiple archive files was happening in the wrong order. Known Issues When running discoverDomain with the -remote flag, there are several MBeans that are not being properly handled that will result in INFO level messages that look similar to the example shown below. These errors seem to happen only when the MBean is non-existent so the resulting model should still be accurate. These issues are expected to be fixed in a future release. ####&lt;Feb 16, 2023 1:40:00 PM&gt; &lt;INFO&gt; &lt;Discoverer&gt; &lt;_add_to_dictionary&gt; &lt;WLSDPLY-06106&gt; &lt;Unable to add ServerFailureTrigger from location /Clusters/mycluster/OverloadProtection/mycluster to the model : Failed to convert the wlst attribute name and value for the model at location (model_folders = [&#39;Cluster&#39;, &#39;OverloadProtection&#39;], &#39;name_tokens&#39; = {&#39;DOMAIN&#39;: &#39;tododomain&#39;, &#39;CLUSTER&#39;: &#39;mycluster&#39;,&#39;OVERLOADPROTECTION&#39;: &#39;mycluster&#39;}) : The wlst attribute ServerFailureTrigger is not defined for the model folder /Cluster/OverloadProtection&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.0.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.1/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.0.1 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes None&#xA;Bug Fixes #1396: Added additional validation to the RCUDbInfo section. #1398: Corrected a bug introduced in 3.0.0 that broke validation of sparse models with dynamic clusters. Known Issues When running discoverDomain with the -remote flag, there are several MBeans that are not being properly handled that will result in INFO level messages that look similar to the example shown below. These errors seem to happen only when the MBean is non-existent so the resulting model should still be accurate. These issues are expected to be fixed in a future release. ####&lt;Feb 16, 2023 1:40:00 PM&gt; &lt;INFO&gt; &lt;Discoverer&gt; &lt;_add_to_dictionary&gt; &lt;WLSDPLY-06106&gt; &lt;Unable to add ServerFailureTrigger from location /Clusters/mycluster/OverloadProtection/mycluster to the model : Failed to convert the wlst attribute name and value for the model at location (model_folders = [&#39;Cluster&#39;, &#39;OverloadProtection&#39;], &#39;name_tokens&#39; = {&#39;DOMAIN&#39;: &#39;tododomain&#39;, &#39;CLUSTER&#39;: &#39;mycluster&#39;,&#39;OVERLOADPROTECTION&#39;: &#39;mycluster&#39;}) : The wlst attribute ServerFailureTrigger is not defined for the model folder /Cluster/OverloadProtection&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 3.0.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.0/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-3.0.0/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 3.0.0 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features #1355: Added -remote option to the deployApps tool that supports deploying applications and shared libraries from a remote machine. (Issue #1312) #1355: Added -remote option to the updateDomain tool that allows configuration changes not requiring archive file changes (except for applications and shared libraries) to be made from a remote machine. (Issue #1167) #1365: Added new verrazzano section of the model that can be used to augment/override the YAML files generated by the Verrazzano-related -target options. (WDT-688) #1367: New archiveHelper tool for helping to create and update the archive file from the command line. (WDT-711) Cleaned up the aliases to clean up online discovery and put tests in place to ensure that they align properly with the various WebLogic Server releases and PSUs. The resulting model from online discovery is now much closer to the one generated by offline discovery. Other Changes #1255: Renamed model attributes to align with the offline naming strategy:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 2.4.4</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.4/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.4/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 2.4.4 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes None&#xA;Bug Fixes #1361: Resolved issue where the custom Coherence configuration file was not placed in the WebLogic Server domain’s expected location. Known Issues Due to the changes made for WDT-663 in WDT 2.4.0, the resulting remotely discovered model contains extra fields that would not normally be there. This is an area of ongoing work to clean up the online aliases to not depend on these extra remote calls to produce a clean model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 2.4.3</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.3/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.3/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 2.4.3 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes None&#xA;Bug Fixes #1356: Resolved Issue where the new ATP Database URL format was causing connections to fail. Known Issues Due to the changes made for WDT-663 in WDT 2.4.0, the resulting remotely discovered model contains extra fields that would not normally be there. This is an area of ongoing work to clean up the online aliases to not depend on these extra remote calls to produce a clean model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 2.4.2</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.2/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.2/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 2.4.2 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None&#xA;Other Changes None&#xA;Bug Fixes #1241: Resolved Issue #1240 that was causing a NullPointerException with discoverDomain. #1252: Reworked the unicode handling to resolve customer issues with 14.1.1 when using non-ASCII characters. Known Issues Due to the changes made for WDT-663 in WDT 2.4.0, the resulting remotely discovered model contains extra fields that would not normally be there. This is an area of ongoing work to clean up the online aliases to not depend on these extra remote calls to produce a clean model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 2.4.1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.1/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 2.4.1 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None Other Changes None&#xA;Bug Fixes #1237: Resolved an issue where the tools supporting the -target parameter were doing target-related work even if the parameter was not specified. Known Issues Due to the changes made for WDT-663 in WDT 2.4.0, the resulting remotely discovered model contains extra fields that would not normally be there. This is an area of ongoing work to clean up the online aliases to not depend on these extra remote calls to produce a clean model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 2.4.0</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.0/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-deploy-tooling/release-notes/release-2.4.0/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changes in Release 2.4.0 Major New Features Other Changes Bugs Fixes Known Issues Major New Features None Other Changes #1193 - Added support for changing the RCU Data Source type during JRF domain creation (WDT-636). #1210 - Improved the speed of remote discovery by bypassing remote calls to determine if a field was set (WDT-663). #1218 - Added -target support for WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 4.0 to generate the domain and cluster schema resources. #1220 - Added support for application modules for JDBC, JMS, and WLDF with normal WDT tokenization mechanisms (WDT-675). Bug Fixes #1194: Resolved an ordering issue when setting the FrontendHost and FrontendHTTPPort with dynamic clusters (WDT-668). #1196: Fixed issue #1170 which was causing an unexpected NameError. #1197: Log a warning when the security provider schematype file is missing (WDT-645) . #1208: Refactored tool exit handling to simplify the logic and resolve various errors. #1209: Resolved an issue with structured applications where the model data was not being honored for the deployment plan file name. #1214: Resolved an issue with structured application discovery causing duplicate override files to show up in the archive file. #1217: Resolved an issue with ATP database support that was not handling connect strings with multiple description fields. #1229: Resolved an alias issue where the TopicSubscriptionParams was incorrectly available on UniformDistributedQueue and not UniformDistributedTopic. Known Issues Due to the changes made for WDT-663, the resulting remotely discovered model contains extra fields that would not normally be there. This is an area of ongoing work to clean up the online aliases to not depend on these extra remote calls to produce a clean model.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>